Remote Web Development Professional

Detail-driven Remote Web Development Professional qualified for Full Stack Coding, Front-End, and Back-End Software Development. Proficient at Website Development and Applications and Game and Animation development. A subject matter expert at Mobile Applications, SQL Database Management and problem solving. Prioritize objectives and apply software quality assurance practices and principles throughout the development life cycle. Support the planning, design, and execution of software testing. Offer recommendations to solve issues. Self-manages performance toward continuous improvement.

Core Expertise

- Full Stack Coding
- Website Development
- Animation Development
- Data Processing

- Front-End Software Development
- Website Applications
- Mobile Applications
- SQL Database Management
- Back-End Software Development
- ► Game Development
- Data Collection
- Problem Solving

Knowledge & Technologies

- JavaScript
- HTML
- CSS
- C#
- Microsoft Office Suite

- Angular
- My SQL
- Typescript

Educational Qualifications & Certification

Earned 54 credits toward Associate of Science Degree (A.S.), Computer Science

South Plains College, Levelland, TX

Relevant Coursework: Business Computer Applications, Introduction to PC Operations, Fundamentals of Networking Technology,
Programming Logic & Design, Advanced Database, Introduction to Computing & Logic

Full Stack Software Development Track Certification

Lubbock Coding Academy, Lubbock, TX, November, 2020

Relevant Coursework: Introduction to Software Development, JavaScript Language Basics, Back-End JavaScript, JavaScript Front-End

Academic Projects

Capstone Project 08/2020-11/2020

Built MVC controllers to provide data to a frontend Angular web application. The data was stored using Entity Framework with SQL and the database was built with EF data migrations. Angular components were created to provide functionality of being able to view and create data through a web browser.

Movie Showtime Application Project

06/2020-07/2020

Created an application that allowed the end-user to choose a movie to view through selection of a category and timeframe.

Professional Experience



Taco Bell, Lubbock, TX
Service Champion

05/2019-10/2020

- Interfaced with 200 customers daily on average to sell fast food and beverages and provide champion-level service.
- Serviced the drive-thru location and the front counter location at 1 restaurant to offer food and beverage products, run the cash register, and closeout orders.
- Trained team members on skills and best practices to improve knowledge of menu options.
- Assisted in the kitchen to put out food, contribute to dishwashing, and setup drink machines.
- Aided cooks in preparing food including air frying as needed.



Sterling Ventures, Sterling City, TX

05/2018-09/2018

Ranch Hand

- Created 4 horse stalls in 1 barn and maintained the stalls through consistent cleaning and supplying fresh hay for feeding purposes.
- Assisted in various tasks that helped the ranch breed horses for barrel racing or sale.
- Built a fencing area that was used to train horses.



Blood Plasma Laboratories, Lubbock, TX

05/2015-12/2015

- **Donor Floor Technician**
- Set up approximately 100 blood plasma machines per shift for usage with donors.
- Stocked the donor floor with supplies including gloves, tubing, and bottles to manage resources and make them readily available.